♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday AD ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
(spaceship blasting)
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot Roll Call ♪
- All right, let's go.
♪ Cambot ♪
Pan left.
♪ Gypsy ♪
Hi, girl!
♪ Tom Servo ♪
What a cool guy!
♪ Croooow ♪
He's a wisecracker.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself, ♪
♪ It's just a show, ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(guitar strumming)
(creaking)
(whooshing)
(clanking)
(door closes)
- Yes yes yes,
well Crow you're not
quite zero Kelvin,
but still it's gotta be
pretty cold in there, huh?
- [Crow] Nah, this is nothing!
Gimme that deep
freeze, mamajama!
- All right, woo!
- Woo!
- Hi Tom, hi Crow, hi
everybody, welcome to
the satellite of love, I'm Joel.
Hey wait a minute, what's
with the Crow in the box?
- [Tom] Oh, we're bringing
his temperature down
to absolute zero!
Seems like it
might be kinda fun.
- Wait a minute,
you can't do that!
If you go to absolute zero,
there'll be no molecular motion,
he'll start a chain
reaction and kill us all!
- [Tom] Well that's kind
of how it played out
in our scenario too.
Wait a minute, that's
kind of stupid, isn't it?
- Yeah it's stupid, we
gotta get him outta there!
(Crow clattering)
- [Tom] Oh good one, Joel!
- Oops.
We'll be right back.
- [Tom] I'm not putting
him back together, either!
- [Crow] I'm shattered!
(theme music)
- Okay, there you go.
Good as new.
- [Crow] Sure, if you ignore
the massive structural damage
and my complete lack
of any resale value.
- Yeah, I was ignoring that.
- [Crow] Oh. Mm.
- [Tom] Oh hi, say would you
guys hurry up with that glue?
It's really starting
to affect me.
- Yeah, okay.
Tabby and Sloppy are calling.
(Crow clattering)
(glugging)
- Oh, Joel.
I was just--
- Doctor?
Have you seen my long underwear?
I'm late for my
ice dancing lesson.
- No I haven't seen your
long underwear, Frank.
And to be perfectly
honest, I wouldn't wear
your long underwear even.
Oh, Joel.
Invention exchange.
Now I've got a nutty idea.
But be a dear and go first,
I need a couple of minutes.
- Sure, if you're not ready
to go, we'll go no problem.
- Good call.
- Geez! (exclaims)
Anyway, my good friend Crow
locked up the deal to do
the music for "The Beverley
Hillbillies" movie.
- Yeah, well we're
hammering out a deal memo.
- And it lead to an
amazing discovery.
- Right, now remember
"The Beverley Hillbillies"
was part of the Paul
Henning-Hooterville trilogy?
- Right, that was "The
Beverly Hillbilles",
"Green acres", and
"Petticoat Junction".
- Right.
- They all had this really
cool incidental music.
- Yeah it was music
that went (vocalizes).
- [Tom] Oh no no no.
If I may Joel, it was
more like (vocalizes).
- The point is, I didn't
know how to make that music
until we came up with.
- The porkerina.
Now don't worry
all you pig lovers,
we didn't use a real pig.
- We didn't?
- No, we just re-invented
the instrument
that made the original
incidental music.
The original was lost in
the tragic Universal fire.
Hey, here comes Mr Henning,
pulling another hilarious new.
(Pinkerina oinks in tune)
- [Tom] Well Mr
Douglas, that there
is a genuine dirt berger.
- That's not a dirt berger.
(pinkerina oinks in tune)
And there's the
official Miss Hathaway.
- Oh, Jethro!
(Pinkerina oinks in tune)
And there's uncle Joey,
he's moving kinda slow.
- [Tom] At the junction.
- Well, pretty hot.
Kinda tired.
Was gonna go fishin'
but it's too damn hot.
Better sit down
for a little while.
Yep, yep.
When's that government
check comin' in?
Pretty hot.
Kinda bloated.
Gonna die soon.
- You're up, sirs.
- Joel.
The human body.
Unattractive?
Sure!
Even worse, it's inefficient.
Especially Frank's human body.
- I'm late for my
ice dancing lesson.
- That's why I've
drained Frank's blood.
- [Joel, Crow And Tom] You what?
You can't do that!
- Don't worry, I replaced it,
with propylene glycol.
Radiator fluid.
I even surgically implanted
a radiator so Frank won't
overheat this summer
and won't freeze
up in the winter.
And you act like I'm the jerk!
- I'm so cold.
- Granted, Frank's
new system does need
to be flushed nightly, but
once you get the hang of it,
it's not quite as
tricky as it seems
and can even be done on an
out patient basis. (chuckles)
(hissing)
(Frank sighs with relief)
- Wait a minute, why
don't you just leave Frank
with his own blood?
That way he can wear a
jacket and scarf and stuff.
- Ant says Frank's blood was
a perviously unknown type,
the money that that
brings in should.
"Why?"
Because it's
science, that's why!
Frank here.
Why don't you run on
to your lesson now?
Come on, go ahead!
Scoot! Scoot!
(chuckles)
Joel, speaking of
unattractive human bodies,
your movie this week,
"Eegah", has got Richard Kiel,
and not much else.
Look, Frank's signed all the
forms, it's an improvement,
he even likes it!
Why, he's probably
out there right now,
skating his little
heart out. (chuckles)
"Eegah". (chuckles)
Oh God.
- Ready?
Holiday for pigs.
(pinkerina oinks in tune)
(alarm buzzing)
(shouting)
Ah, we got movie (shouting)!
(cranking)
(whooshing)
(creaking)
- [Tom] I'm Charles Kuralt,
and we're going to leave you
with this shot of a flower.
- [Joel] "Cactus Flower"
with Goldie Hawn!
(ominous music)
- Hey, it's Scattergories!
- [Tom] Urgh, look the
sign is leaking. (exclaims)
- [Joel] That was Art Clokey's
first study of Gumby there.
- Yes, you too can
learn how to play
the guitar in two easy lessons.
(gibberish in movie)
- [Tom] Oh this must be that
Grunge look from Seattle.
It's from Seattle, I've heard.
- [Crow] Is that a real
poncho or a Sears poncho?
- [Joel] Richard Kiel as
Eegah Templar, the saint.
- [Tom] Focus it.
Focuses please, Helen.
Hello?
The smoke is for focus?
- Harriet, the
cattler's smoking again!
- [Joel] I'm dead, don't smoke.
- [Tom] Wait a minute,
they got Delans
flippin' us off, here!
Hey back at ya, Clyde!
- [Crow] Otis Nixon!
- [Joel] He looks like
thin William Hickey.
- [Tom] Shaking the bush, boss.
Hey actually, you seem
to be exhibiting sort
of ineluctable defenestration
of characters in (mumbling).
- [Joel] Poppies
will make us sleep.
- [Tom] Mm-home, baby.
- Welcome to the crypt!
We've dug something
up for you! (laughs)
Why not stick around
and watch "Dream On",
it's the breast
show on TV! (laughs)
Kill me.
- [Tom] Stop him.
- [Joel] Boy, this looks
like it's really gonna
be scary what with the smoke
and flowers and everything.
- [Tom] Creeping effects.
Circle Pines after
dark. (beatboxes)
- It's Frederick's of Maplewood.
- [Tom] The Loretta Young show!
(Crow exhales)
(Joel vocalizes)
I'm young and free
and feeling fresh!
- [Crow] Taxi!
Oh, I drove. (chuckles)
- [Joel] I forget,
can I drive a stick?
Oh.
- [Joel] It's the flying sob!
- I think it's a
bug-eyed sprite.
And so is she.
(car engine rumbling)
(Tom mimics car engine rumbling)
(car honking)
Honk if you love "Eegah"!
- Hi Roxie!
- Sorry about my face!
- I thought I was supposed
to meet you up at the club.
- Well you still are!
I just bought myself a
new swimming suit tonight.
- Can I wear it?
- Oh?
- Yes.
See?
(exclaiming)
That?
- [Tom] Sex appeal!
- Well I get off
work in 10 minutes.
- Follow me out then.
- Follow you?
- Sex appeal!
- Listen I change clothes
and beat you out there!
- Ha!
(car engine rumbling)
- Again, sorry about the face!
- That's my girl.
Her father's Robert I. Millar.
- [Joel] Yeah, I just
pump my gas, butthead.
- You oughta see her swimming.
- Hey!
- Hey, put that
in the way back, my
kids are back there!
- I don't know why, but I
wish he'd pistol whip him.
- [Tom In Movie] Gee,
I sure am sorry, sir.
- [Tom] But I'm
sort of an idiot!
- I was thinking about
having dinner with my girl.
She lives up at the club.
- [Tom] Yeah, with
Robert I. Miller!
♪ 77 Sunset Strip ♪
(Crow mimics "77
Sunset Strip" theme)
♪ How will you make
it on your own ♪
- (mimics honking) I've got
a new swimsuit everybody!
- [Tom] Oh no, she's
chasing down Emmett Kelly!
- [Joel] Suddenly,
she began to doubt
the whole bathing suit purchase.
- [Tom] Eegah!
(all exclaiming)
(dramatic music from movie)
- [Tom] My fault,
sorry, all my fault.
- [Crow] I'm with
Allstate, who are you with?
Ach, mein Gott,
the schwannstucker!
- [Eegah] Nova.
- [Tom] Which way
to Bly workshop?
(Eegah speaks gibberish)
- [Joel] You know I heard Kiel
ad-libbed this entire scene.
- [Tom] Funny, I was
drivin' a stick too.
Ha ha!
- [Crow] Damn foreign cars!
- [Joel] Well there's something
you don't see every day.
- [Tom] It's the hose clamp,
you wanna get that checked
when you get back to town.
(dramatic music in movie)
- Oh forget it, I'm going back
to sleep. (mimics snoring)
- [Joel] I found
this in your grill,
it probably was causing
all that trouble.
- [Tom] Oh, you had a root beer
and a side of fries with that?
- [Joel] Nah, Eegah
can't go with that,
not much leg room, mm-mm.
- Say, could you give me a lift
to Stephen Jay Gould's house?
- [Tom] Jim Morrison,
the Paris years.
- [Joel] Oh, he's
doing tai chi on her.
(horn blaring)
(Eegah exclaims)
(Eegah speaks gibberish)
(Roxy screaming)
- I'm still making payments!
- [Joel] Busted!
Saved by the 'Vette.
- [Tom] Hey Eegah!
How you doin', buddy?
(Roxy screaming)
- Roxy, it's me, Tom!
- [Tom] That's why
I'm screaming. Ahh!
- [Roxy] Tommy! Oh!
- [Tom In Movie]
What's the matter?
What happened?
- [Crow] There was a
Poco song on the radio.
- Is he gone?
- [Tom In Movie] Who?
- Is he?
- [Tom] Dis me?
- I don't see anybody.
Just take it easy and
tell me what happened.
- [Joel] Is she really
going out with him?
- Well I did!
Honest, I saw a giant.
- Oh, that face, I feel
handsome in comparison.
- [Tom] You know the nice
thing about this car is
she can fold it up
and put in her purse.
It's compact.
- [Joel] Crate and Barrel?
- No, it was right in
the middle of the road.
Not a half mile from here.
- William Faulkner!
- [Roxy] He doesn't believe me.
- You didn't really expect
anyone to, did you Miss Miller?
- Why not?
It's the truth.
- [Tom] Oh! Good comeback.
- Honey, pre-historic monsters
are rather large
order to swallow.
- Dad, I didn't say
it was a monster.
He was a giant.
- [Tom] It's a big difference!
- You know, a caveman.
- Club and Orly?
- [Roxy] Yes.
- What my daughter saw, she saw.
Now let's just
let it go at that.
- [Tom] Could you just
take our order, please?
- Well if you see
the giant again,
let me know in time
to take some pictures?
- [Tom] Eat it, the old foe.
(theme music)
- Come to Eegah retirement
village, for the good life!
- [Joel] Town, caves and slack
heaps starting at $100,000.
(mumlbing in movie)
- [Roxy] No.
- Let's be realistic about this.
You said yourself
that you fainted.
Isn't it possible that you
dreamed this whole idea?
- No, Dad, I didn't!
There was a giant!
- [Joel] She's gonna need
(drowned out by movie).
- Now I don't wanna call
this story of ours a
lot of foolishness,
and I haven't so far, have I?
- No.
- But if there were a
giant, if anyone at all--
- [Tom In Movie] Mr Miller!
Come 'ere!
- [Tom] My neck snapped!
- What you find?
- [Tom In Movie] I don't know,
it sure looks like
a foot print though.
- [Roxy] Well lemme see!
(dramatic music swells)
- It's dirt!
- [Roxy] Dad, look!
There's the heel,
and there's the toe.
- [Joel] That's an
ant colony, you idiot!
- [Robert] Look at
the size of that.
- [Joel] Glenn was
fifty feet tall.
- It must have been made by--
- Say it!
- A giant.
- What did I tell you?
- Hurray, I won!
(Roxy kissing)
- And that's for finding it.
- I'll find the big
boy himself for ya,
if you feel like that.
- He left the road, right here.
- [Unknown Speaker In
Movie] Watch out for snakes.
- [Tom] Who said that?
- [Joel] Let's not forget
where we parked supercar.
- [Robert] Better
go back to the car.
- [Roxy] No!
He's my giant.
(mysterious bass music)
- [Tom In Movie] Holy cow,
he was standing right
here watching us!
- Playing base.
- And then he turned,
he took off for...
- [Tom] There?
- Shadow Mountain.
You suppose that where he lives?
♪ Oh, to live on
Shadow Mountain ♪
- [Robert] That accounts for his
never having been seen before.
- It's too bad we didn't the
dune buggy, to go after him.
- What for?
- I could get some pictures.
Maybe even bring him back.
A lotta people aren't gonna
believe this giant jazz.
- No, we're not sending
about this, you understand?
- Why not?
After the way everyone
laughed at me.
- Your turn will come.
- He's got third degree burns.
- I'm going up on Shadow
Mountain with a camera.
- Are you gonna write a book
about the giant, Mr Miller?
- [Robert] That's
the idea, Tommy.
- [Tom In Movie] I'll
take ya up there,
my dune buggy's all ready to go.
- No thanks.
- It is, I just
gave it the works.
- There's no offense, son.
- [Joel] Damn it, Son.
- But I'd like to take
this trip in something
a little bit safer.
- [Tom] More stylish.
- [Joel] (exlaims) He
resents my dune buggy!
- [Tom] Watch out for snakes.
- [Joel] "Whirlybirds"!
- [Tom] "Blue Thunder"!
- "M*a*s*h"!
- [Joel] "Apocalypse Now"!
- [Tom] "Dispatches"!
- 'Cause you see,
it's a helicopter.
- [Joel] (laughs) and
all of those elements.
(whirring in movie)
- [Tom] Looks like I got a
flat tire here. (chuckles)
- I'll see you in about
two days at the most.
- Well please take
care of yourself.
- Now my credit cards
are in the desk drawer,
you make sure you
leave 'em there.
- [Joel] Dad's fun.
- This things supposed to
be safer than my dune buggy?
- Oh shut up about your dune
buggy, you little twerp.
- All right, let's go.
- I like them, yeah.
- [Joel] Got my
shoe trees in here.
- Ouch, my hands! (exclaiming)
(helicopter whirring)
- [Tom] Richard Nixon
leaving the White House.
(Tom and Crow vocalize
"The M*A*S*H Theme")
- [Joel] I thought we promised
never to do that again.
- Sorry.
- I had my fingers crossed.
Look at those legs!
- [Joel] Boy, they're
really hittin' it off.
(helicopter whirring)
- [Tom] Hey skipper, look at
this thing on my leg here,
it's like a mole but it keeps
flakin' off, you see that?
I want that!
- [Joel] Now, there should
be a Ram Charger up there.
- Oh, for a shoulder
mounted anti-aircraft gun.
- [Joel] Oh you mean a Stinger?
- Whatever.
(helicopter whirring)
- [Tom] Commute to work or play
in your own personal helicopter,
here at Acrylic Bubble
makes it possible!
- [Joel] Eegah drives a tank?
- Well, I really don't
know what to say, Roy,
look this isn't goodbye really,
there are other
helicopter rides.
- [Joel] So you got everything?
- [Tom] Surprise!
I am Jose Greco!
- Now don't you forget,
I want you to meet me
at mouth of deep canyon
tomorrow at four.
- [Joel] (laughs) Sure,
four, whatever. (laughs)
(dramatic tone)
- I sure hope it
doesn't get hot.
- [Tom] Geez, the helicopter
took off fast, where'd he go?
- [Joel] Hey, to the left!
Yeah, there.
- Hey, that's my daughter.
- [Tom] See those are
his contact lenses,
he's quite
near-sighted actually.
- Meet him at deep mouth
canyon tomorrow at four.
What the hell was I thinkin'?
- [Joel] Oh yeah,
you can tell he's
an experienced mountaineer.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] What the hell?
Is that a Bell Huey?
Whoa, flashback's kicking in.
Dang.
- Better tell others.
Wait, there are no others.
(Eegah exclaims)
- [Joel] The Old Indiana
Jones Chronicles.
- [Tom] Watch out for snakes!
- It's Lawrence of Pasadena.
(chuckling)
- [Joel] Oh man look,
he's wearing corrective
shoes with black socks.
- [Tom] He's wearing
corrective everything.
(mysterious music)
- Oh, this is a Kodak moment.
- [Joel] Okay, say "Ambers."
(music gets rhythmic)
♪ They took the whole
Cherokee nation ♪
- [Crow] This is
gonna prove a lot to
the royal geographic society.
- [Joel] Howard Hughes?
(dramatic music)
- Victim of this
own fashion sense.
- No!
- [Tom] No means no, Eegah!
- Oh no, no, no!
- It's under a big W.
(Roxy yelling)
- [Tom, Joel And Crow] Eeee!
(water splashing)
- [Joel] What?
Oh, it's a Tampax commercial.
♪ I love you, Vicky ♪
(Tom, Joel and Crow
exclaiming in disgust)
♪ You don't do ♪
You know maybe you should
move those amps away
from the pool?
- He's surrounded by
adoring housewives.
♪ For the first day we met ♪
♪ Was my last day ♪
(Tom's joke is
drowned out by music)
- [Joel] Brian Jones!
♪ Vicky ♪
- What?
♪ Oh Vicky ♪
What?
Shut up, you're embarrassing me.
♪ What have I done ♪
- [Tom] Would the
gentleman by the side of
the pool please just
continue this song
and watch out for snakes.
- [Joel] Johnny Winter and...
- Look Mom, watch me!
- [Joel] Man, looks
like it hurts to be him.
♪ Don't love me ♪
♪ I was a fool ♪
- [Tom] People in
those rooms are calling
the management right now.
♪ Oh Vicky ♪
- No, that comes right
from the sewage systems!
- [Joel] I'm so naughty.
I'm such a little brat.
Hm-mm.
- [Tom] He's like a
Cabbage Patch Elvis.
♪ Vicky ♪
♪ Oh Vicky ♪
(Tom, Joel and Crow
mimic "Jaws" theme)
♪ I'm so alone ♪
♪ If you ♪
- Oh, there you are.
♪ could just talk to me ♪
♪ If I could just call you ♪
- [Joel] Did you
enjoy my frolicking?
I'm naughty, you know!
♪ Would you give ♪
♪ one more chance ♪
(Tom is drowned out)
♪ To a fool ♪
(Tom, Joel and Crow
mimic dogs barking)
♪ Oh Vicky ♪
(creaking)
(whoosing)
(clanking)
(door closes)
- Ow, gee!
- Oh gosh, I'm sorry pal.
I've been so distracted,
I just keep thinkin' about
that slick gas station
in today's movie.
D'ya notice how sleek
and beautiful it was?
- Oh gee, no Joel, I
can't say that I did.
Coo-coo, coo-coo.
- Hey come on, I'm serious.
There existed a time when
our nation took pride
in its service station.
They glean like a beacon of
hope from coast to coast.
And one day, ka-blewy.
You know Sky Chief Super
Service turned into
the tank and tummy.
I don't mind telling you guys,
the day this country went
self-service was the day
that hell began to bubble
up and flood the Earth.
- Oh, I hate to burst
your bubble, Joel,
but what about the
bubonic plague?
World War?
Stalin?
- Well come on, those
were all big things.
You know Hell works better
when it's a lot more subtle.
Give you an example, okay.
Crow, what do you
think of Adolf Hitler?
- Well I hate him naturally.
- Right, now what do you
think of the band Sticks?
- Well you know they
had one or two decent,
oh my God you're right.
- I get it now, Joel.
Now I'm not certain when
Hell started for me,
but I think it has something
to do with Christopher Cross.
- Yeah, yeah.
Remember the time that
Charlie Reaver died
and it wasn't even
in the papers?
- Yeah.
- Or when the 86 jarts.
- I think the first time
Flow said, "Kiss my grits,"
something inside all of
us withered and died.
- Usually Joe Camel to
sell cigarettes seems like
a pretty ripe slice of Hell.
- Yeah, I agree with
that, and then there was
the time Denis Leary
released "No Cure For Cancer"
as an album.
And then the time Vicki
Lawrence won a Grammy for
"The Night The Lights
Went Out In Georgia".
- I know I stand alone on this,
but the say Blansky's
Beauties got canceled.
- Yeah, you stand alone on that.
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Sinbad's pretty icky.
- Yeah, what about the
Charlene Tilton workout video?
- Joel, what chance
do we have on a world
that keeps presenting us
with vivid images of Hell?
- Well, there's personal
liberty, strength of conviction,
those have been known to work.
Then there's the time
the country rallies
to beat back Hell,
like the time we as a nation
said "No" to Yahoo Serious.
- I remember that.
All of us together, drawn
explicably the slobbering mouth
of Hell, and then suddenly,
somehow, by some unknown force,
rescued in the nick of time
like Moses and Israelites.
- Now who in creation is
powerful enough to do that?
- Gee Davy, do you
think it was God?
- We'll be right back.
- Ow!
(theme music)
(chattering)
- [Tom] Oh look, she's dressed
for a Benny Hill audition.
- [Joel] Harry Connick Jr.?
- Hello?
- [Tom] Hey, Eegah, (gibberish)
- Yes?
Dad'll understand.
- Ew!
- It's one of those things.
- Jonny Quest.
- Just a minute please.
- [Joel] What?
- Do you where Duke Canyon is?
- Yeah.
(chuckling)
- Are you sure?
- Sure I'm sure, I've
been there lots of times.
Why?
- Don't worry, Mr Kruger,
I'll take care of it.
- [Crow] Can I have some
money for some Chuckles?
- Thanks for calling.
- [Tom] Bye bye.
- What's up?
- That was Mr Kruger
from the airport.
The helicopter blew a
gasket or something,
he won't be able to pick Dad up.
- At Duke Canyon.
- I pledge alliance.
- Yes.
- To your Dad.
- No problem, we'll
get the dune buggy,
we'll whiz right out there.
- [Joel] I've got
it, he looks like
the bat from "Ferngully".
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] Rat Patrol, in
three or four colors.
- This is whizzing?
- Wait'll we get
off the highway.
- [Crow] Joel, do you ever
whiz out in the desert?
- [Tom] Hey, it's Schlepcar.
(Tom in movie is drowned out)
- But there's no road here!
- This is what the
buggy was made for!
- [Tom] It's swell for tearing
up fragile ecosystems, watch!
- It looks like Sheltering
Sky meets the Archies.
(swanky music)
On their way to Thunderdome.
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
- [Tom] Oh!
I gotta go!
(Roxy is drowned out)
- [Tom In Movie] My ties
are filled up with water.
- [Roxy] To keep them cool?
- [Tom in Movie] No, the weight,
gives me traction in the sand.
Watch this!
- [Tom] Huh.
- Oh yeah, that
really is something.
Would you just drive, please!
(Roxy screaming)
- [Joel] I think she's in pain.
- [Crow] Put a wallet
under her tongue!
(Tom pretends to throw up)
- [Joel] Dad can
wait, this is a blast!
- [Roxy] Wee! Wee!
- [Crow] Stop that,
don't do that!
- Wee!
- Oh, are they carrying a pig?
- [Roxy] Come on, Dad's waiting.
- [Tom] Oh forget
Dad, we're young!
What about us?
- We have to talk
about our relationship.
- Wee!
- Stop saying "Wee,"
nobody says "Wee"!
- [Joel] Oh, this is a real Lucy
and Viv situation right here.
- Wee?
- [Joel] You know, they should
throw some snow under those.
It's a switcheroo!
- [Tom] Fun's over,
we're gonna die now.
(dune buggy engine revving)
(Roxy laughing)
- [Crow] I was afraid we were
gonna have neck for a minute.
(swanky music)
- [Joel] Hey neat, the
music got us out of trouble!
♪ Got a groovy
thing goin', baby ♪
- [Tom] Hey, you know, if
this was a Mountain Dew ad,
wouldn't they be water skiing
on roller skates being pulled
by horses off of cliffs?
- [Joel] Wee.
- [Crow] Welcome to
Death Valley Days.
- There you are, Duke Canyon.
- I don't see Dad any place.
- [Tom] Okay, let's go.
(Tom riffs)
- [Joel] The endless bummer.
- [Roxy] It's past 4:30.
- [Crow] See?
- [Tom] I wonder
whose hand that was.
- [Crow] I don't know.
- [Tom] To be with the hu-man.
To live like the hu-man.
- [Crow] Just making a place
to set your Dad's body
once we find the remains.
- [Tom in Movie] Hey take
it easy on that water.
- [Roxy] Well I don't want it
to dry out before Dad gets here.
And don't you eat any more!
- [Joel] And don't
touch my soup starter,
it's gonna cook for a while.
- [Tom] Do you think we'll
freeze to death before
the jackals get us?
- [Roxy] What do
you suppose happens?
- [Crow] He died.
- [Tom in Movie] Oh
nothing happened.
He's not coming on
a bus, you know.
Can't expect him to
be right on the dot.
- [Tom] Don't make
me think so much!
- [Roxy] He should have
mood it before dark.
- [Tom in Movie]
Don't worry about it.
He'll see the campfire
and come walking
on us any minute now.
- [Roxy] That's what
you said two hours ago.
- Well, he will.
- Well if you believe that,
what's the idea
of the bed rolls?
- [Tom in Movie] Look,
I carry all this junk in
the buggy anyway, so you might
as well get some use out of it.
- I'm not sleepy.
- [Joel] I'm petulant!
- [Crow] When Edward Albee
dabbles in beach movies.
- Lie down, take a
rest for a while,
I'll keep the fire going.
- [Tom] I'll just break
off pound of my hair at
a time and burn it.
- Hey, what are you
doing with that?
(Joel exclaims)
- I always carry a gun
in the desert.
There's coyotes around the camp.
- Put it away, we're
not playing cowboy.
- You know there's mountain
lions around here too.
- And the elephants and stuff.
- Well they won't come here
a fire, I know that much!
And I'm not going
have you take a shot
at something and it
turns out to be Dad.
- Okay, okay, I'll put
it away on one condition,
that you crawl
and get some rest.
- Okay!
- [Tom] I won't
shoot your Dad, okay?
Geez!
(wind howling)
- [Joel] Roxy?
I'm going to sing
myself to sleep.
- He borrowed that top
from Audrey Hepburn.
(whistling music)
- Arch, no, no Arch,
no please, God, no please.
- [Joel] She's packed
to move and can
be dropped shipped to
your home overnight.
- [Crow] Fortunately
he remembered to bring
the Isley Brothers.
- [Tom] He's got kind of
a MIDI Silvertone
working there, huh?
- [Crow] He went on to do
music for Sergio Leone.
(Joel mimics whistling)
I'm death and I have
visited upon you.
♪ If I had a
thousand paintings ♪
- [Joel] Well you don't!
♪ In a marble ♪
- [Crow] This should
keep the wolves away!
- [Tom] I would be in
the Museum of Modern Art.
- [Joel] Dum-de-dum.
What the hell is that?
♪ Would be-- ♪
- [Joel] Hey stop
smiling, he's smiling!
- [Tom] That's nice honey,
where's the 12 gauge?
♪ By the moons are
good, they say ♪
♪ And so's a gallery ♪
♪ But I'd be like tiger on-- ♪
- [Crow] I've heard enough,
I'll go beat him senseless.
♪ I couldn't stand tomorrow-- ♪
- [Joel] Shouldn't he
be moving his lips?
No, I'm not gonna
kill him right away.
I'll let him linger.
♪ Half a mile away ♪
♪ If I had a billion dollars ♪
- [Crow] They'd raise
my taxes. (chuckles)
♪ Salary ♪
- [Tom] He makes Debbie Boone
sound like Hound Dog Taylor.
♪ I'd spend it ♪
- [Crow] I've figured it out.
He's a cyst with teeth and hair.
- [Joel] I demand
you stop smiling!
- Now, is she Billie Jo,
Betty Jo or Bobbie Jo?
(Tom in movie whistling)
- [Tom] Please come
on Eegah, hurry up!
Where's that club?
- [Tom, Joel And Crow] Eegah,
Eegah, bonk bonk on the head!
(theme music)
♪ Archie's here ♪
♪ Duh-duh-duh-dun-dun ♪
- One way or the other,
what'd you think?
- I don't know.
- [Joel] I've never
thought before.
- I'll climb up the ways, see
if the buggy can get through.
- [Crow] Or shovel.
Didn't ask to be in this movie.
- Naw, you better stay here.
- No!
- There's no reason
both of us going,
we gotta come back
for the buggy anyway.
- Well then we'll come back,
I'm not gonna sit
here doing nothing.
- Oh, women!
- [Tom] See, what do
they mean by that?
- You stay here with the buggy.
- Nope.
- And drive it up to meet me
when I give you the signal,
that'll save us both a trip.
Come on!
- [Crow] I'm
whining you, please!
- Okay.
The gun, toss it.
- [Joel] Now your
lunch, toss it.
- [Tom] I can see it
coming, a tragic accident.
Come on, come on!
- Oh.
- Damn!
- Gimme a blast of that
horn if you see anything.
- Don't worry about that.
- [Joel] You know, he's built
for child-bearing, isn't he?
- Serpentine! Serpentine!
- [Joel] I see a cactus! Honk!
I see a lizard! Honk!
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Keep going
you sap, just over
that ridge, that's it.
I'm outta here.
- [Joel] Stay alive!
Whatever may occur,
I will find you!
- [Tom] See?
I told ya so!
Watch out for snakes! (chuckles)
- [Crow] (babbles) Come on, boy!
Just a little closer.
Mm, smooth pink meat.
Shorts too, nothing
but meat on that boy.
♪ La la la la la ♪
- [Joel] I do wanna look
good for you. (sings)
- [Crow] Why am I losing
my hair in big chunks?
- [Joel] (sings) Oh
nice steering wheel.
I don't know about all this.
Oh it's sunny.
My dress is blue.
Oh nice shovel.
Dum dum dum dum.
What about my nose hairs?
- [Crow] You're
here, and he's got
the traveler's checks there.
- [Joel] Archie's
in the Gaza Strip!
♪ This is my country ♪
- [Crow] What was I
looking for again?
Sky?
No woman, I should have
wrote that note to myself.
It's weird the way it's so blue.
Hm, what are those
buzzards circling?
(wind howling)
♪ Born free ♪
(Roxy screaming)
- [Tom] What's that smell?
Is that me?
Oh. No?
(car honking)
- [Crow] Don't hit!
Oh he knows women and she's
gonna want that purse.
- [Joel] This is really hard,
fighting the caveman, owie!
- [Tom] Oh my gorilla shins, ow!
- Roxy!
- Music!
- And elsewhere!
Oh I let another one.
- [Tom in Movie] Roxy!
Roxy!
Where are ya?
- [Crow] I'm being abducted!
- [Tom] You know, Eegah
should have taken two trips,
first for the purse and
the club, then the girl.
Would have been easier.
- [Crow] Oh boy,
I made good time.
- [Joel] Oh no, he's
got people stacked
like cordwood in there!
- [Tom] He is this close
to being Dom DeLuise.
- Oh, I see you've meet Eegah.
He'll spoil you, I'm spent.
- [Joel] Visit Cave of
the Mounds, Dodgeville.
- [Crow] That's
okay, don't help.
- [Tom] Yep, yep.
This looks much better over
here by the lime deposit.
- [Joel] Eegah, I woke
up, you weren't here.
I hate that.
(mysterious music)
- [Crow] Eegah, you
said you lived alone.
(Tom mimics "Wedding March"
like a caveman grunting)
There, play nice.
- Roxy!
- [Joel] You finally break
up with that weird faced kid?
- Roxy!
- [Tom] I got it, don't worry.
- Poopy!
- Roxy!
- Dad!
- Oh, she can snap in and out
of consciousness, can't she?
- [Roxy] Oh Dad!
- Oh!
- Oh, are you hurt?
- [Tom] No, I wear this sling
for effect, you doorknob!
- Here, let me help you.
- [Joel] Ow!
That's okay.
- How did you even get here?
- We came looking for you,
and we were both so worried
that we didn't know what to do.
- No, no no.
No, no no--
- [Tom] No, just the choke.
- She's mine.
♪ The doggone girl is mine ♪
She's mine.
- He understands you.
- I dunno, we've got a
beautiful friendship going.
- Is that irony, Dad?
(Eegah grunting)
- [Tom] What's he saying?
Shimmy shimmy coco pop?
- (gasps) Dad!
- Oh no, this guy went to
the Torgo school of fondling.
- Me scare him?
- You might!
- [Tom] Mm, smell
Love's Baby Soft.
- [Joel] Now you
smell him, honey.
(Eegah sniffing)
Scent of a woman.
- He likes your perfume.
- Smell all you want.
- [Tom] But take all you smell!
- What became of the others?
- What others?
- You didn't come out
here alone, did you?
- No!
- Tish, that's French!
- Tom's with me.
I mean he's out
there some place.
- He's just curious.
- [Joel] Aw, he's
pawing me, Daddy!
- [Tom] That's okay, precious.
Eegah like get caught in rain.
- It's real, see?
- [Joel] Honey, I've been
telling him about you.
♪ How do you do, oo-ooh ♪
- [Roxy] What's he doing?
- Looking for lice, I believe.
(Roxy exclaims in disgust)
Careful, honey.
Take it easy.
He won't hurt you.
- He hurt you!
- No, I did that myself
when I fell on the camera.
- [Joel] What a great dad.
- You better break this
up before I scream!
- Tell him you're hungry.
- I'm not.
Well think of the alternative.
- [Tom] That's it, I'm leaving.
- I'm hungry.
- [Joel] 'Cause I thought
of the alternative.
- Hungry.
- I've ramen noodles and
brown mustard, that's it.
- [Joel] Well go
ahead, just tell me!
- [Crow] Two words! Movie!
Sounds like.
- [Tom] Would you like
the see the titles again?
- [Crow] I'll just have a salad.
- What are those?
- Those are his relatives.
- [Tom] Well
they're really lame.
- [Joel] I am William Burroughs.
- [Crow] I am William Burroughs.
- [Tom] I am William Burroughs.
- [Crow] I'm Rose Kennedy.
- They're dead.
- Yes, apparently for some time.
- Eegah, eegah.
- It's always so awkward
meeting the family.
(Crow chuckles)
- [Crow] Vowels, Eegah!
We need vowels!
- [Tom] I'll make the daiquiris.
- Come on Dad, let's
make a run for it.
- Didn't work.
The entrance is blocked.
- (exclaims) What
are we going to do?
- I don't know.
- [Joel] First of all,
you can quit leaning
on my broken collarbone.
- [Crow] Oh, great.
Dinner's a Duraflame log.
- He's telling his
family all about you.
- [Joel] He's actually
a pretty funny guy.
- He told them
about me last night.
- [Tom] You shoulda been there,
we really got the
giggles, we cried.
- Think how lonely he must be.
- Yeah, he should get
into league bowling.
- I know whatever he
is, he's a human being.
- [Crow] Norman?
Who's the girl, Norman?
Who is she?
- [Tom] It's Wilfrid Hyde-White.
Oh, yes, she seems
a very nice girl.
Properly superb.
Capital, yes, smashing, yes.
(Eegah speaks gibberish)
- [Joel] Uh-huh,
yes, she's Catholic.
- [Tom] It's either
German or he's burpin'.
- [Crow] My three skulls!
(Joel vocalizes "My
Three Sons" theme)
- What do I do?
- [Robert] It'll be all right.
Play it by ear, don't let him--
- [Tom] Sorry, you have
to sign tough for my son.
- [Joel] Literally.
- How do you do?
- I'm really really dead.
- [Tom] Oh, and there's Red.
- [Robert] Well,
that one looked like
a very important ancestor.
Shake hands with him, Roxy.
- Oh Dad!
- I'm kidding of course.
- Pleased to meet you.
He doesn't know they're dead?
- He suspects.
- I think so.
But he can't make
himself accept it.
- I'm not having any trouble.
- [Tom] Make his
mouth move, sweetie.
I'll make the funny voice.
(Crow chuckles)
- Oh, that's fine.
- Joel!
- I know, I know.
(theme music)
- Why not try two
hands in the club?
- Okay you guys, I'll
all set up in this thing.
What was it for again?
- [Tom] If you must know, Joel.
We're going to surgically
alter your face so you look
just like Arch Hall Jr.
- Wait a minute,
who's Arch Hall Jr?
- You don't know?
Arch Hall Junior, the butt-ugly
teen star in today's movie.
Now this might hurt a bit.
- [Tom] Oh Dr Gypsy,
patient needs gas!
- And how are we today?
- Oh what a nice
big boy you are.
He's toast, see you
guys in post-op.
(Crow purring)
(Tom grunting)
- Ah yes, let's get
cracking, Dr Tom.
Once that gas wears off,
I don't know how long
those restrains will hold.
- [Tom] Don't give it
another thought, Dr Crow,
by the time Joel comes to,
he'll have no recourse but
to take up a career as
a wimpy B-movie actor.
(Crow and Tom laughing)
You know, Doctor?
- Yes?
- I have a mad posh to
start with the Arch hair!
- Switching on Archer.
Oh, and it smells bad too.
Now quickly, Dr Tom.
Let's smoosh his face up to
look like sunburned baby.
- [Tom] A must!
Sunburned baby, I told
you to face, coming up!
- [Crow] Mm, looking
good, Dr Tom.
But he needs that inhuman
Play-Doh color skin.
But how?
- [Tom] Don't fret,
Dr Crow, the pigment's
on its way, watch, Doctor!
(Crow laughing)
Yes!
- [Crow] Ah, the
sleeper awakens!
Hurray, he's almost complete.
I'll give him the Archer
nose and let's get him
the hell out of here.
- [Tom] Yes, yes, yes, yes.
- I don't wanna Arch Hall Jr!
- [Tom] Our last battle
and quick, Gypsy!
Hit 'em with the fixative!
(Gypsy yelling)
It's almost--
- It is?
(alarm blaring)
(yelling)
(clanking)
(whooshing)
(creaking)
- [Joel] Ah!
You know that really hurt?
- Sorry.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Wait.
Who am I?
What am I?
Why am I?
Who am I looking for?
- [Tom] Well, about
that time old Coyote
had a hankerin' for
some grubs. (chuckling)
- [Crow] This old desert stinks,
I can't find one clean spot.
- [Joel] (sniffing) Mm!
I smell something oily and pink.
- I can't eat any more of this.
- Fake it.
- That's what I've been doing.
Now I'm getting sick.
- [Tom] And talking
like Loretta Lynn.
- Eegah.
- Is that his name?
- It might be, that what
he says most of the time.
Eegah.
- [Joel] He also says the
word rayon, which is weird.
- Oh Dad, no.
- [Crow] Want aperitif?
- [Roxy] That's all I need
now, a drink of gluck.
I don't know how anybody
could drink whirl of gunk.
- [Tom] You tried Crystal Pepsi?
Some people will drink anything.
- [Crow] Put lime in
coconut, drink all up.
- I guess it can't hurt me.
- [Tom] (mimics
drinking) It hurt me!
- Just last as long as you can.
He won't hurt you if
you're doing something.
- A pre-historic gentleman, huh?
Thank you!
- [Joel] It's a sipping drink.
- Well, here's to you!
- [Tom] Up yours!
- [Crow] Thanks.
She's gonna get the
Eegah trotts for sure.
- You have to be strong to
drink in the first place!
- [Tom] Can I get a
beer back with this?
- No, I'm still thirsty.
Thank you!
(Eegah grunting)
(Roxy exclaiming in disgust)
- [Joel] Come on,
soup good food!
- [Crow] Sarah T, portrait
of a teenage alcoholic.
- [Tom] No no, honey.
I need some ReNu.
My contacts are killing me.
- [Robert] What is it?
- Believe it or not, Dad, I'm
going to look at his etchings.
(Tom, Joel and Crow
exclaim in disgust)
Nice!
No no no, this.
- [Crow] Oh you like that one?
I don't even like to show it.
It's the lineal.
- [Tom] This Cubist,
heavy Braque influence.
- [Joel] Look there's
a ripple on that rock.
- [Tom] Apparently Eegah
covered the cave with muslin.
- [Crow] Oh wait, wait,
this one really good.
- [Tom] In time before
born, live man sail sea.
- Dad!
- What is it?
- This guy's good!
- Look at this drawing!
It's me in my car.
- [Crow] Oh it is her!
- This one.
It's me!
- [Tom] That's what she thinks.
It's actually Sandra Dee.
(Eegah grunting)
- [Tom in Movie] Roxy!
Roxy!
- [Joel] Hey, maybe
you should move around
a little bit, Arch?
- [Roxy] This Eegah
makes me drink anymore of
this sulfur water, I'll die.
- We've got to keep him busy.
- I know.
- Come on, barkeep.
- And it's not so bad
as a matter of fact,
a little bitter.
But seems to have a certain
quality that's good for you.
I wouldn't be a bit surprised
if surfer in these walls
is what's kept these giants
alive all these years.
- You mean these giants
- You know, even in crisis,
- (drowed out)
- these two are dull.
- Where have you
seen those before?
- [Tom] The Keith
Haring exhibit.
- In that cave in France.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
(Crow chirping)
- Same styles, same everything.
- Same bat-channel!
- definitely pre-historic.
- [Joel] No duh.
- Yes, I'd say that he and his
tribe have always been here.
- Are there others?
- No, he's the last one.
- [Joel] And where will his
seed find purchase?
- How can you be sure?
- Take a good look
at his family.
From the condition
of the shrowns, I'd
say the last one died
50 or 100 years ago.
- How come this clown knows
more than Richard Leakey?
- How old does that make him?
- I wouldn't know the answer.
♪ Eegah with the laughing face ♪
- [Joel] Today,
ladies and gentlemen,
Eegah is 400 years young.
- [Crow] He's been there
since the beginning of time
and he's only drawn
tree pictures?
(Eegah grunting)
- [Joel] Here, you
take the couch.
- Here it comes.
- Wait for it.
- [Eegah] Stem-lo.
- [Tom] Stem-lo,
stem-lo, oh stem-lo!
Oh!
- [Crow] This is the dark ridge
school of primitive mating,
you'll get used to it.
- [Joel] Crime time after prime
time is on, can we watch it?
- No.
(Eegah yawning)
- [Tom] We get it, Eegah,
we're just not tired.
- [Crow] "The Big Sleep"!
"No, Six Pack"!
"Long Day's Journey
into", oh, pass.
- [Joel] I wanna sleep
with the woman, get it?
Do I have to put on my
Marvin Gaye album or what?
- [Tom] I don't know honey,
he didn't do this with me.
- [Crow] What are they doing?
- [Joel] They're
telling secrets, honey.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] Oh Ted,
someone's watching.
- [Crow] What?
Can I help you?
- [Joel] Roxy!
Roxy!
(Crow mimicking
bewildered gibberish)
- [Tom] Man, hold on
to my dental early!
- [Joel] I think he's nesting.
- [Tom] Good instinct.
- [Crow] Oh yuck!
He's groomin' himself.
- [Joel] How?
- [Tom] Well, back to
another day of whinging.
- [Joel] Okay, get out hair oil.
- [Tom] I feel like
I'm getting close
from (garbled gibberish).
- [Crow] Hey!
- [Joel] Basic-H from Shaklee.
For all your liquid needs.
- [Tom] Day's
gettin' away from me.
Roxy!
Roxy! (whines)
(dune buggy engine rumbles)
- [Tom] Watch out for snakes!
♪ Good morning, good morning, ♪
♪ we've talked the
whole night through ♪
- [Crow] This movie isn't
healthy for children
and other living things.
- Roxy.
Roxy!
- Honey, you're sleeping
on the commode, honey.
- Roxy!
(Roxy screaming)
- [Crow] Arch Hall
Junior, get away.
- [Roxy] It's you, Dad.
- Go to see if the
rock's been placed.
He's gone, now's our chance.
- [Joel] I'm up, Dad!
Guy!
- [Tom] We should take a knife
and cut through the canvas.
- [Roxy] It's there.
What are we gonna do?
- [Crow] They're in a
saggy cave that leaks.
- [Roxy] What can I do?
- [Robert] Help me.
I gotta sit down.
No no, don't touch it.
- It's mine!
- It's gotta be tied up
or something, doesn't it?
- There's some
asprin in my ear bag.
- [Roxy] I don't see it.
- He brought it here,
must be around some place.
- [Joel] It's the red thing
that's not pre-historic.
- [Tom] Why don't you ask
uncle Dave over there?
- [Robert] Keep looking.
He probably hid it somewhere.
- [Crow] It's a cave, how
hard do you have to look?
- [Roxy] Oh, here it is.
- [Tom] It was over
here in his armoire.
- [Joel] Hey, I
got a crazy idea,
let's rearrange his
family while he's away.
- The aspirin's in
that small pocket.
- [Crow] Dad, why did you
bring your bowling ball?
(Robert coughing)
- I'm sick.
- Gimme two.
- [Tom] Oh no no, keep 'em
comin', come on, come on.
- [Joel] The classic
asprin scene.
- Drink a lot of water.
Food gives you strength!
- [Crow] And there's
hardly any rat in it!
- Knit bones, honey.
- It's got to be tied up
or something, doesn't it?
- No, feels pretty good.
- Liar!
- That's no way to
talk to your father.
- The trouble with
you is I spoiled you.
- You sure did. (laughs)
- [Joel] Good God, I suck.
- [Tom] Hollywood Hot Tubs 3!
- With Kelly Monteith.
- What do I do?
- Nothing.
I'll just sit here.
- How about if I
washed your face?
Or gave you a shave?
It'll make you feel better.
You've got all your junk here.
- [Crow] I know it's
weird, but I'm into weird.
- Okay.
- [Joel] A shave it is.
- [Tom] Sad really.
- [Joel] Say, isn't it
about time Tom got back to
the gas station?
- [Tom] He's on sabbatical.
- [Joel] Oh.
- [Crow] Patience my ass,
I'm gonna kill somethin'.
- [Tom] Is this some kind of
a weird biathlon or somethin'?
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Roxy!
(coughing) Roxy!
Roxy!
- [Joel] Ew! No!
- [Tom] Joel, I gotta
slap this movie so hard.
- [Crow] My dog!
Ah!
Oh! Oh.
- [Joel] This is so sick.
Oh, please become Sweeney Todd,
please please become
the demon barber
of Fleet Street right now.
- [Crow] Have you
seen "Andalusian Dog"?
♪ I have often walked
down this street before ♪
- [Joel] They're on a collision
course with wackiness!
- [Crow] Roxy! Roxy!
I got that swimming
suit rash! (whines)
- [Tom] There goes
one stupid young man.
♪ Red roses for a blue lady ♪
- [Tom And Crow]
Eegah-shaka, eegah eegah
eegah-shaka eegah eegah.
♪ I can't stop this feeling ♪
Eegah-shaka.
- [Joel] Oh it's just Eegah.
- Look, before he has a
chance to block the entrance,
I'll get his attention,
you run him out.
- And leave you?
- Do as I tell you!
- Not this time, Dad!
- Pappa, don't preach!
- You were lucky last night.
He's had time to
think about you.
- [Tom, Joel And Crow] Ew!
- You could get
your head bashed in.
My father didn't
raise me that way.
- [Crow] Nah, nah, nah!
(bubbling)
- [Joel] He's covered with
foam again, continuity!
- [Crow] Eegah honey,
father's here for dinner.
(funky guitar music)
♪ Warden threw a party
at the county jail ♪
- [Joel] Honey, did you bring
home some milk and bread?
- [Crow] A poem,
by Henry Gibson.
- He brought me flowers.
- We've got to get his
mind on something else.
Make a production
out of it, think.
Come on, whistle, come on.
(Roxy singing)
- [Tom] Am I being
punished for something?
What could I have done?
I didn't ask for this movie!
- [Joel] Honey, when's
your Dad moving out?
- [Crow] Kinda weird,
shavin' her Dad, isn't it?
♪ La la la la la, la la ♪
- [Eegah] Ogah.
♪ La la la la ♪
- Strauss?
♪ la, la la la la ♪
- He's interested.
He almost forgot
to shut the door.
- Well, that doesn't say
much for my sex appeal.
(Roxy singing)
- Stop singing!
Stop singing!
- [Crow] First blade lift
hair, second one cut clean.
- [Robert] Ah-ha!
- Now I suppose
he wants a shave.
- [Robert] Good, give it to him.
- Anything to please a customer.
- [Joel] Does anybody else think
this show's sick just to Eegah?
- Eegah!
- Yeah.
- [Tom] Just use some
spirit gum remover.
- [Joel] Why don't you
just cut the string
that holds that beard on?
- [Robert] Try these.
- [Crow] They're toasted.
- [Tom] I've got a
Flowbee in here too.
- [Joel] I know what lads do.
Let's feather it.
- [Tom] Oh baby, oh yes,
you know what I like, yeah.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom in Movie]
Roxy, where are you?
- [Crow] It's a
giant gila monster!
- [Tom] He's starting to
look like Markie Post.
- [Tom in Movie] Roxy!
- [Joel] Oh, he's calling
all the animals to help 'em.
- [Crow] Hey, I got
a message from Roxy.
She said to hang on.
- [Tom] Oh boy, this is
one of Eegah's
problem areas here.
- [Crow] Eegah like so
much he buy company.
- [Robert] Better watch
him with that shaving foam.
- [Joel] Eegah's
gonna do Whip-Its!
(exclaiming)
- [Crow] It's perfect!
- [Tom] So who do you like
in the big game tonight?
- [Joel] I am big game.
(exclaiming in disgust)
- Make him stop!
- Ah! Oh!
- [Crow] That's not a
tongue, it's a musky leech!
- [Joel] For once
I'm glad to see 'em.
- Roxy!
- [Tom] You don't have to
wear that dress tonight!
(gun blasting)
(Crow mimicking car
engine rumbling)
- Roxy!
(Crow mimicking explosion)
- She shaved his chest!
- You did a better job
with shaving him, Roxy.
- [Roxy] Thanks!
- [Robert] There's no way of
telling how that fun it makes.
- [Joel] I like Ike.
- [Crow] Mm, me look like
Anthony Michael Hall.
No, more like Sandra Bernhard.
- [Joel] This could be a
real cute engagement photo.
- [Tom] Try parting
it on the left.
- [Eegah] Eegah, eegah.
- [Crow] Dad, were you talking?
- [Roxy] You're handsome!
- [Joel] Well, I
wouldn't go that far.
- [Eegah] Eegah.
- [Tom] Set the hook, Roxy.
Foam side, edge side.
- [Robert] I warning you, Roxy.
Don't upset him.
- Tell me some more
about your etchings.
- [Tom] Man!
- [Tom, Joel and Crow] Boo!
- [Tom] Boo!
- [Roxy] You like
the pretty smell?
Here, this is
loaded with perfume.
- [Joel] Yeah, it's
probably Giorgio.
- [Crow] What a femme.
- [Joel] This
imposter fragrance!
- I'm going to try to
get him to move the rock.
- [Tom] Between love and Fred
Flintstone lies Obsession.
- These smell pretty too.
Where did you get them?
Out there?
- [Tom] On the exit ramp?
- Yes, I really think you
should put this in water.
- [Joel] Don't patronize me.
- I guess you're right.
There are plenty more out there!
- [Tom] I didn't know
Senator Packwood was so tall!
- See? Take it.
I'll bet you haven't seen
anything like that before.
- [Crow] He he, pretty, he he.
- Don't you think it's pretty?
- [Joel] I'm bunching.
Do you mind?
- Give him something else.
(Tom, Joel and Crow
exclaiming in disgust)
- [Crow] Dad!
- What?
I haven't got anything else!
- [Crow] Except for some
cheese-filled Combos.
- [Joel] Okay, you drive
a hard bargain, lady.
- That was a mistake.
- [Crow] Turn it off!
- [Tom] I hate to think
what Camille Paglia
would say about this.
- Don't you get
the idea I don't like
you, but my father.
- [Crow] He might
shout something at you.
- [Roxy] He can see us!
Ee!
Yeah, that's the idea!
- [Tom] That's exactly
what I've been saying!
- We could go outside.
(Eegah grunting)
- [Joel] What a dope!
- No!
- [Crow] Didn't you
say take out Dad?
- No, Eegah.
I'll die.
(theme music)
(Eegah grunting)
- So how are you
kids gettin' along?
(Eegah yelling)
(Tom, Joel and Crow booing)
- [Joel] I'll kick ya.
- [Crow] My collarbone!
Watch the collar, oh!
(Roxy screaming)
- [Crow] Calls all units,
domestic in progress
by the canyon.
- [Joel] Well she's showing
more courage than her Dad.
(gun blasts)
- [Tom] Who did that?
- [Crow] Help me, Spock.
- [Joel] Oh, it's this clown.
Uh-huh.
- [Tom] No, he wouldn't
fit in the den.
- [Crow] The Chianti is gone.
- [Tom] Will someone
help me with the door?
Please?
♪ Rag doll, Daddy's
little cutie ♪
- [Joel] Owie, owie,
sting, oh, ouchie.
My pants.
Ah!
- [Crow] Ah!
The collarbone!
Don't you know first aid?
- Get after him.
- The dune buggy is
just down the canyon.
- Oh!
- (drowned out) go on.
- [Joel] Don't forget
your little satchel.
- [Crow] That purse will
be the death of him.
- [Tom] The dingoes
took my baby!
- [Joel] Coulda just
carried my wallet
in my pocket, I suppose.
(Eegah yelling)
- Surprise!
Happy birthday.
- [Tom] All part of his
drop your guns program.
- [Joel] Ew, I don't
wanna do that again.
- [Crow] You hurt
Eegah's feelings.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Oh poopy!
Oh double poopy!
- Yes! Yes!
- Yeah! Woo!
- [Crow] Yes!
He is resting comfortably now.
- [Joel] Yes!
- [Tom] You wanna another shot
at me, Eegah, you big femme?
- [Joel] Come on,
you stupid Zinj!
- [Crow] I'll throw
this grapefruit at you.
- [Tom] Oh!
Right in the area.
- [Joel] Oh, Eegah, I thought
you were, (screaming).
- Oh!
- Cool it, Roxy,
everything's all right.
- [Joel] Tom, I wanna start
seeing guys from other eras.
- [Roxy] Dad!
- He's okay, he's
waiting for us.
- [Crow] You got a chorus
petal in that purse?
- [Joel] Carrie.
- [Crow] Can't keep
a good Eegah down.
- [Tom] Oh!
It's a paper cut.
Most embarrassing
day of my life.
- [Crow] If you prick
Eegah, do he not bleed?
- [Joel] Well, I pretty
much saved the day there.
Mm-hm.
- [Tom] Well, got the
bagel bungee down!
It's not going anywhere.
Bom bom, bom bom bom.
Ah, the good life.
- Hi, kids!
- Hi, chicken Dad!
- Dad!
- [Joel] Bill Clinton legs.
- [Tom] Take off
the pith helmet.
- Run kids, run!
- [Tom] Dad, don't lower
your voice like that!
- [Crow] Oh yeah, I
see what you mean!
(Eegah yelling)
- [Joel] Top o' the dune, Ma!
- [Crow] Shovel's safe.
- [Tom] Dad, quit wriggling
on my seat like that!
(dun buggy engine stuttering)
- [Crow] Oh no, the
oldest cliché in
the movie, they're doomed.
- [Robert] It won't start!
- [Roxy] Let me!
- [Tom] Hello, Hall family!
I'm not letting you
leave without some
of this yummy hot dish!
- [Roxy] Hurry!
- [Robert] What's wrong with it?
- [Tom in Movie] I rig it
so nobody can steal it.
- [Roxy] Out here?
- [Tom] At least take some
of these nutty caramel rolls!
- [Joel] You're supposed
to drive away from 'em!
- [Tom] Bernie, catch
up with that one.
All llama, cow.
♪ Oh you pretty
Chitty Bang Bang ♪
♪ Chitty Chitty Bang
Bang we love you ♪
- [Crow] Goldurn
smoochers in my property!
- [Tom] What's this?
Eegah ogling our allies?
Callus Cro-Magnon conniptions?
- [Joel] Is it okay
if we still go "Wee"?
- [Crow] Well let's wait
'til we outrun him first.
- [Tom] What about
this three bean salad?
It'll go bad!
- [Joel] What, what?
Okay, bye.
Wait you guys forgot my
purse, we have to go back.
- [Crow] Over to your right,
the Robot Monster set.
- Dead end.
(Tom, Joel and Crow sing
"The Pink Panther Theme")
- [Joel] What's with the
whimsical sitcom music?
(car honking)
- [Tom] Hey, stupid
caveman dude,
read between the lines, man.
(Eegah grunting)
- [Crow] Run, Von Ryan!
(Roxy screaming)
- [Joel] Buh-bye then, don't
forget to stay in touch!
Bye.
Okay.
- [Tom in Movie] Which way?
- Start with away from him.
- That way.
(dune buggy engine rumbling)
- [Joel] Hey, did I tell ya my
tires are filled with water?
My tires are filled with water.
(dune buggy engine rumbling)
- [Roxy] Look!
(dramatic tone)
- Hi, I'm back!
- [Tom] Oh, now where are you?
- [Joel] You know, goodbyes
are hard for Eegah.
- [Tom] Here, have
some Irish soda bread!
- [Crow] I thought for
sure that would hit them!
(dune buggy engine rumbling)
- [Joel] Hey, you're
going the wrong way!
- You okay?
- Honey?
- Just fine, Dad.
- Wow-wee, there he is!
- [Tom] Yep, pretty much.
- So long, high pockets.
- [Tom] The tall jokes
are funny, but they hurt.
♪ Torn between two lovers ♪
♪ Feel like a fool ♪
- [Tom] Stay alive!
Whatever may occur, I--
- [Joel] I covered
that one earlier.
- [Tom] And as we left
the Clam Flowage Desert,
somehow we knew that
we would return,
hunting for the mighty jacks.
(relaxing music)
- Well, back to the cave.
Lost my girlfriend,
got my Eegah crushed.
I've been working on my beard
since 3000 BC, and boom!
It's gone.
Eegah have bad day.
(steam rushing)
(creaking)
(whoosing)
(cranking)
(door closes)
- Mm, mm, mm, mm!
This is gonna be good.
You know it's as much fun
to make as it is to eat.
- Well I hope it tastes because
the "as much fun to make part"
just isn't happening for me.
- Say Joel, I got a question
about today's experiment.
You know that Roxy chick
hangs out with her Dad a lot,
but where's her mom?
- Oh well I'm sure
Dad's a widower.
- Well how do you know
he wasn't divorced?
- Well because the movie
took place in the 60s,
and back then divorce
was considered
socially unacceptable,
and so the entertainment
industry's elegant solution
was the untimely
death of a spouse.
- You know, you're right Joel.
Now that I think of it, the
families on TV back then
were mostly run
by widowers, huh.
I mean think of it, guys.
"The Andy Griffiths
Show", "Mayberry RFD",
"Courtship of Eddie's
Father", oh "My Three Sons",
"Flipper", even "The
Beverly Hillbillies",
the list goes on and on.
- The only normal family
back then was "The Munsters".
- So, what happened to all those
spouses on those 60s shows?
I mean geez!
Back then marrying a
good natured suburban guy
with cute precocious kids was
like, buying a one-way ticket
to an early grave!
- Well I know that
on "My Three Sons",
Steve Douglas'
wife's untimely death
had something to do with
secret project X-15.
- So how about uncle Charlie?
Did he have a dead wife?
- Well he was secretly
married to Bub,
who died under
mysterious circumstances
that were hushed up
by the government.
- Now you're making stuff up.
- Just push the corn.
- So what about Mr.
Eddie's father's wife?
What hap-a?
- Oh you mean Mrs Livingston?
She tragically died leaving
the Earth's atmosphere
running away
with my favorite
martian, it's sad really.
- Now you're making stuff up!
- Yeah.
- When you come
right down to it,
what we're really
talkin' about here guys
is a cheap plot device
that enables young swinging
bachelors to mix it up
with hot young lady, and
still have adorable kids
that they can dispense
folksy homespun advice to.
- Yeah, I guess it was
all pretty harmless.
- Wait a minute, what
do you mean "harmless"?
An entire generation grew
up watching shows run
by single parents.
No wonder the nuclear family
has exploded in recent years.
- Hey, I just
thought of somethin'!
We don't have a mom either!
- Well hey, yeah!
We're latch key bots!
(Crow and Tom crying)
- Come on you guys,
gimme a break, come on,
I'm stranded in space.
Besides, when I was a kid I
saw the ABC movie "The Week"
with Herschel Bernardi, but
I don't wanna get married
and it had a profound
effect on me.
- Don't worry, Joel.
We both know we have a
lot to be grateful for.
We have you, we have Gypsy.
Cambot, Magic Voice.
But most importantly, we
have lots and lots of love.
And that's somethin'
you just don't get
a two parent household.
- This thing wasn't even on.
- Oh!
- We'll be right back.
(theme music)
(dramatic music in movie)
- [Crow] What is this, a
prehistoric Endless Love?
- [Tom] Criminy, I lived next
to Palm Springs all this time,
didn't even know it. (chuckles)
- [Joel] Wait a minute.
Why do they have a statue
of Pat Nixon in there?
- [Tom] What's he gonna do?
Match the swatch?
- [Crow] We're closed, sir!
- [Joel] Oh man, I gotta
get ahold of myself.
I'm getting hot
over a mannequin.
(Eegah grunting)
(Eegah sniffing)
- It's cold and distant.
- [Tom] Ah well.
Geez, the heck with her.
Taxi!
(car brakes screeching)
- Look out, there's
a Foley artist!
- [Tom] Watch out for snakes.
- [Joel] Econo Lodge, but why?
(jazzy music)
- [Robert] Roxy!
- [Tom] Honey, why
do we have an oven
in the living room?
- I'm ready, Dad!
- Well I'm not.
You're gonna have to help me.
I can't manage the tie.
- Here, I'll do it.
Does it have to be this one?
- Young lady, that happens to
be one of my favorite ties.
- But the color.
- You gave it to me.
Four years ago.
- Boing!
- Wa, wa, wa, wa.
- Why, it's lovely!
- [Crow] Jerry
Garcia designed it.
- [Joel] Dad, whatever
happened to Mom?
- Are you sure you're feeling
well enough to go out tonight?
- Honey we've got to go out.
- Well it's not
anything special.
It's just a party.
- Your whole gang will be there.
- Yeah.
- You can't avoid
them forever.
- [Tom] But you should.
- Some of them (mumbling).
- We'll find old Agnus
Pennison, she'll laugh a lot.
- [Crow] Hello!
I've got your Girl
Scout cookies!
- [Joel] Oh this is some of
his best acting right here.
- What'll happen to him?
- I don't know, but I'm certain
we're doing the right thing.
If we were to reveal that
a giant actually exists,
there'd be a whole army
out there tracking him down
like an animal.
- No, they wouldn't!
We wouldn't let them.
- Honey, he's from another age.
Anther eon.
- [Crow] Like me!
(banging)
- Come in!
- [Tom] Hi, it's me Eegah,
say my hands are full,
can you grab somethin' for me?
- Hello Mr Millar!
- [Tom, Joel and Crow] Ew!
- Wow-ze-wow, wow!
- [Joel] Oh, I can
feel his eyes on me.
- You sure look swell, Roxy.
- Thank you.
- [Tom] She looks like
Stockard Channing.
- I'll only be a minute.
- Is something wrong, Mr Millar?
- [Crow] Sit down, pie face,
it's a long list.
- We were just talking
about our little adventure.
- Oh, I see.
- [Robert] You do?
- Well sure.
Girl like Roxy don't get over
a thing like that right away.
- [Robert] Doesn't.
- That's what I say!
She's gonna get her mind of it.
And this hop tonight can help.
- [Robert] How?
- Yeah, my combo's
gonna be there!
Man, they swing.
- [Joel] I'd like
to meet your combo.
- I'm ready.
- [Tom] Wowee, wow, wow!
Oh.
- Well let's split then.
- [Crow] Ah sir, why
do you have an oven
in your living room?
- Mr Millar, I got my
Dad's wheels tonight.
- Really?
Do they fit on your car?
(Tom, Joel and Crow
laughing sarcastically)
- [Tom in Movie] You're
funny, Mr Millar.
Real funny.
- [Crow] I'm gonna
kill you last.
- Gr.
- [Joel] Sure,
whatever, let's go.
(quiet sneaky music)
(glass shattering)
- [Joel] There's not
even any glass there.
- [Eegah] Eegah!
- [Crow] Oh this place
is a piece of cake.
- [Eegah] Eegah!
- [Tom] Where's their
collection of dead people?
- [Eegah] Eegah!
- [Crow] Man, these
people live like pigs.
- [Joel] Hey, check it out.
There's an oven in
the living room!
- [Tom] Paddling go long way.
- [Joel] It looks like Gregg
Toland photographed this.
- [Tom] That's a
trulligan, here we are.
- [Crow] Ah, missed 'em.
I'll leave a note.
(Eegah sniffing)
- Um, I'm in here!
(Eegah exclaiming)
- [Tom] He's really gotta go!
- [Crow] How do
these work again?
Twist or pull or push?
(dramatic music)
- Here's Johnny!
(banging)
- [Joel] Oh, it's
a US Homes home.
(lots of women screaming)
- [Tom] What, 50 women in there?
- [Joel] Hey, it's
an all meat buffet.
- [Tom] Yep, that's right.
No decorations, no plus seating,
just meat and meat setups.
- [Crow] Sir, the horse
radish is on the side.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Wow! Who?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Let's get outta here!
(they talk over each other)
- [Joel] let me tell ya.
- [Buffet Customer]
Call the police!
- [Joel] Ray Bolger, no!
- [Tom] Oh, seconds.
- Hey wait a minute, friend!
What is this?
A masquerade?
- That is Miller's
giant darling.
(Eegah grunting)
- Aw come on, you can
talk plainer than that.
- I'm sorry sir,
take that outside.
(Red suit man is drowned out)
- What did he say?
- He's real!
- Of course he's real.
(screaming)
- [Joel] Hey, no
horse play on deck!
- [Unknown Speaker In Movie]
Wait, call the police,
there's a giant here.
- [Tom] Take one caveman, a
buffet and a swimming pool,
and you've got Caveman A-Go Go!
- [Joel] The life guard
saw you, you know!
(laughing)
- [Crow] Eli Stevenson!
Duh-duh-duh-duh.
- [Radio] Large man or
giant creating disturbance.
(car engine sputters)
- [Tom] I have no idea
how I started the car.
(siren blaring)
- The dumb blue line.
(jazzy music)
♪ At the old rock house
on the Brownsville Road ♪
- [Crow] So, when
does the combo of
the really swings show up?
♪ You turn to the left
at the sign of the toad ♪
♪ To the empty old house
on the Brownsville Road ♪
- Ready, steady, bite me.
♪ The old rock house on ♪
♪ the Brownsville Road ♪
♪ Crazy things happen
according to the code ♪
- [Joel] Excuse me?
(theme music)
- I just wanted some
fresh air, that's all.
- Is it honey?
- Fresh, I mean?
- [Tom] I'll go to
the papers, Daddy.
- No.
Dad, I've got the
funniest feeling.
- [Joel] Downstairs.
- What is it?
- [Crow] You know, stuff.
- I can't describe it.
I just know something's
happened to him.
- Him?
- Eegah.
- [Tom] Who's Eegah?
- The Giant.
- Oh, yeah.
- Or whatever he is.
Something's happened to him.
- Roxy, look at me.
I love you very much.
- Wish I could
- You're more like
- return the sentiment.
- your mother every day.
Every living thing was
her personal concern,
and she worried about them.
- [Crow] I gotta go tan now.
- That's just it, Dad.
But you see, worry isn't
the feeling that I have.
- [Tom] It's my nausea.
- I don't know what it is.
He's a creature.
Well you just have to
look at him to see that!
He even tried to kill us.
- [Joel] But basically
he's a good egg.
- But I.
- You can't get him
out of your mind.
- [Crow] Bonk!
- [Tom] Is this The Third
Man all of a sudden?
- [Joel] Oh, Eegah's
a mall walker.
(Tom mimicks Eegah)
- [Crow] Always go back for it.
- That's my job for about
two more years, if I can hold
on to you for that long.
Then it will be up
to somebody else.
- [Crow] Hey, Richard
Speck is there!
- Maybe him, huh?
- No!
- Hey, where you been?
I was doping out a tune
just for you in there.
I look up, and you're gone.
- We can hear every word, Tom.
I said here, do not understand.
(sirens blaring)
- You're funny, Mr Miller.
Really funny.
- I'm being sarcastic.
- Come on, Roxy, let's dance.
- Wait a minute.
- What's the matter?
- I thought I heard sirens.
- Aw, that's Deano's
Sax, it leaks.
(dramatic riff)
- Looks like the grifters
meets "Quest For Fire".
(sirens blaring)
(screaming)
- [Crow] Snoop
Sisters, me hate 'em.
Mildred Natwick, pah!
- [Tom] And hate George Gobel.
Eugh, George.
- Oh no, don't.
- [Crow] Oh boy, that was close.
- [Joel] Hey, it's
Wilma Flintstone's mom.
- [Crow] Let's take
another peek, Eval.
- [Tom] Hello Mr Giant, sir,
with the stick there
upstairs, hello?
- [Joel] Oh crap, my room's
always by the ice machine.
(sirens blaring)
- [Crow] I'm sorry, Gary,
I had the wrong page of
the Hudson street map.
- [Joel] Hey, generic cops.
(siren blaring)
- [Tom] They're cheaper
than regular cops.
(dog barking)
- [Joel] Oh the sheriff's
barking out orders.
(Crow laughing)
- [Cop] Charlie, look out!
- [Crow] You two
are on your own!
- [Joel] Bunny slippers.
(screaming)
- Oh don't do that!
- Abner, I saw a giant!
(dramatic riff)
- Come to bed, Gladys.
- Don't shoot, Charlie!
(rock music)
- [Joel] I guess she's
working through her grief.
♪ Looky look looky ♪
♪ Look at my thorax ♪
♪ Looky looky looky ♪
♪ Look at my torso ♪
♪ Tequila ♪
- [Tom] He walked
out on his own song!
♪ Tequila ♪
- [Crow] This band has more
personnel changes than Menudo.
- [Joel] It's a tag team band.
♪ Tequila ♪
- [Crow] No, oops.
- If I didn't know
they were dancing,
I'd swear this was a fight.
- What?
- I say it looks like a fight!
- Well you're a good dancer.
- [Tom] Quit bogarting
that joint, Floyd.
- [Crow] Where'd my date go?
Oh there you are.
♪ Torso ♪
- [Joel] Well, shall we?
- [Crow] You askin'?
- [Joel] Come on, you clown.
- [Crow] I'm with you, bud.
♪ Together forever and ever ♪
- [Crow] Wait a minute,
something's wrong here!
Where's my girlfriend?
♪ Tequila ♪
- [Joel] Can I have
my date back, please?
Thank you.
- [Crow] (strains) Not as strong
as I used to be. (strains)
♪ Tequila ♪
- [Fighter] I'm gonna hit you!
(punching)
- [Tom] Oh!
Hey, how come I don't
get Foley?
- Knock it off, she's my girl!
- [Fighter] I'm gonna smack!
- [Crow] You!
- [Tom] Hi everybody!
(dramatic music)
- The Hat Squad.
(shouting)
- Get him!
- Invitation didn't say where
or actually I didn't get one.
Hope it's okay I crashed.
- Eegah!
Eegah!
- Oh, it's looking
like Altamont all over again.
- No, don't!
- [Crow] Don't
drink the last beer!
- [Fighter] No!
- No, no!
No!
- [Tom] Just push
him in the pool,
he's probably got
tubes in his ears.
- [Joel] Man, she gets
picked up so much,
she should have a handle.
- There have is!
- Halt!
Halt or I'll fire!
- [Joel] The guy
looks like a toy!
(Crow chuckles)
(gun blasting)
(screaming)
- Don't shoot, he
doesn't understand!
- [Crow] Oops, too late.
- [Tom] At your
Lincoln-Mercury dealer!
- [Joel] We're all
out of Chex mix!
- [Crow] That's a
strange thing to wield!
(gun blasting)
- [Tom] Hey Mom, watch me
Mom, (garbling), watch me!
- [Joel] We're gonna need
a really big skimmer.
- [Crow] Upsie-daisy!
(Tom, Joel and Crow
exclaiming in disgust)
- [Crow] He's an evil specter!
(somber music)
- [Joel] So, how
about that drink?
- [Tom] Mood's gone, Floyd.
- [Robert] Toward.
- [Crow] He tampered
in God's domain.
- [Tom] Ironic, bastard never
saw an in-ground pool before.
(tutting)
- [Tom in Movie]
Remember, I love you.
- Who said that?
- Where'd he come from?
- [Party Attendee] Is he real?
- [Party Attendee] Who is he?
- He's dead.
- Yes, he was real.
It says so in the
book of Genesis.
- [Joel] By Phil Collins?
- [Robert] There were giants
in the Earth, in those days.
Chapter four, verse 32.
- [Joel] Oh, that's
totally out of context!
- [Crow] Oh.
(Tom sighs)
(coughing)
- [Crow] I feel
sticky and dirty.
- [Tom] I feel filthy, my
very soul has defiled--
- [Joel] That's okay, guys.
We'll get y'all
cleaned up, okay?
- [Tom] Okay, I've gonna go.
(Crow babbling)
- [Joel] All right!
- [Tom] Go!
(creaking)
(whooshing)
(clanking)
- [Crow] (crying)
Hurry up, Joel!
Turn the water on!
I've gotta wash "Eegah" off me!
I'm naked and afraid.
Hey, don't look!
- I can feel that slimy
moving all over me!
Urgh!
It's wearing an Urline
sweater soaked in cat liver
on a hot (garbling).
Sir, would you be
a dear and turn
the shower message
head on pulsate for me?
- [Joel] Got it, yeah.
- [Tom] Thank you. (cries)
- [Crow] Hey, pass me a
Fels-Naptha, would ya?
- [Joel] Okay, got it.
Here she comes.
- [Crow] Thanks!
Hey, there's a hair on this.
- [Tom] We don't have hair.
(Crow and Tom
exclaiming in disgust)
- Okay, boy you guys,
if you could just,
get nice and clean and
I'll read this nice letter
and that'd be nice.
Okay.
- Okay.
- This comes from Lina
Rought and Nancy Page,
let's put that on still store.
And a picture on still store.
And it says, "Dear
Joel and the bots,
"This missive is winging
its way to you from two
"of your very devoted fans.
"We recently watched 'The
Day The Earth Froze,'
"where the search for a SAMPO
was pivotal to the movie.
"You expressed a desire
to know what a Sampo was,
"so we felt obliged to send
photos of an actual SAMPO.
"See enclosed."
Okay, and there's the picture
was us right on the SAMPO.
And that comes from Lina
Rough and Nancy Page.
- Woo!
- Oh boy!
I feel like a new man.
Washed that movie
right off of me.
- It's amazing what a little
soap and water can do.
- Okay, what do you think, sir?
(cranking)
- Ah.
(metallic dinging)
Oh not now, Joel.
Daddy forgot Frank's regularly
scheduled maintenance.
All the coolant leaked out.
Seized right up.
Just got the thing
paid for, too.
- So do you think maybe
I could possibly get
my blood back, please?
- Oh, you want your blood back?
Fine!
Baby, baby, baby!
I'll put your blood back in,
I'll pour it right back in.
Come on!
Come on, Frank.
- No no, you know what?
I don't even want it anymore.
You take it.
- Yeah? Let's go!
No, I insist.
Here's your precious blood.
You take it, you big
stupid, you bully blood!
- That's it!
You know what?
I'm going to push the button.
- Oh you're going
to push the button?
Go ahead, push
the button, Frank.
- I'm pushing it.
- Push it then, I dare you.
Need your mommy?
- I am pushing the button.
(whooshing)
Oh.
(horn music in
tune to theme song)
- Drink it.
- That's what I've been doing.
Now I'm getting sick.